artreview.com 2019-04-10

# privacy / ArtReview

### Art Review Ltd.

ArtReview Ltd. Is a privately held company and is committed to protecting your privacy. We have prepared the following policy outlining practices undertaken when you provide your data to us.  

 **Who we are:**

Art Review Ltd. is a registered company in England 02720767

 **Art Review Ltd head office is based at:**

1 Honduras Street, London EC1Y 0TH, United Kingdom

 **Brands currently published by Art Review Ltd.:**

ArtReview

ArtReview Asia

artreview.com

1\. What information do we collect from you?

1.1 How do we collect this data  
1.2 Personal information we collect about others  
1.3 Cookies

2\. How will we use the information that we collect?  

3\. Do we share your information with third parties?

4\. Changing your mind about marketing services and keeping your details up to date

5\. Where is your information processed and how do we keep your Personal Data secure?

6\. Access to your Personal Data

7\. Question regarding this privacy policy

8\. Changes to this Privacy Policy

Art Review Ltd. collects Personal Data and Anonymous Data when you visit our websites or when you send us information or communications. “Personal Data” means data that allows someone to identify you, including, for example, your name, address, telephone and mobile numbers, e-mail address, as well as any information about you that is associated with or linked to, or could be linked to, any of the foregoing data. “Anonymous Data” means data that is not associated with or linked to your Personal Data. Anonymous Data does not permit the identification of individual persons. We collect Personal Data and Anonymous Data, as described below  

 _How we collect Personal Data_

We collect Personal Data from you, such as your name, contact details, country of residence, zip code or post code, gender or birth date when you register on one of our sites or when you choose to use the various services we provide. We also collect other types of Personal Data that you provide to us voluntarily, when, for instance, you make a purchase, respond to surveys and questionnaires, or enter a competition. If you provide us feedback regarding our sites or services via e-mail, we will collect your name and e-mail address in order to send you a reply.

In order to improve our services to you, we may ask you to voluntarily complete confidential surveys. We do not ask you to provide us any personally identifiable data in association with these surveys although we do associate your responses with Personal Data. If you do not wish to participate in a survey, however, simply decline to participate when asked.

 _Personal Data that we collect from you about others_

If you decide to invite a friend or family member to join any of our services, we will collect your name and e-mail address as well as your friend’s or family member’s e-mail address in order to contact them by e-mail. We will always ask your permission if we want to mention your name when contacting your friend or family member. This information is used once only and is not saved in our database, unless they have entered a competition or other promotion in which case their e-mail address is stored only for that purpose. If you decide to invite a friend or family member to become involved we will collect and save their e-mail address into our database, along with their contact preferences, as we would for anyone who registers on our sites.

 _Cookies_

“Cookies” are small pieces of information that a website sends to your computer’s hard drive while you are viewing a website. Art Review Ltd. uses cookies to provide you with a more personal and interactive experience on our sites. You have the ability to accept or delete cookies, but please be aware that for some parts of our site to work, you will need to accept cookies. For more information on cookies please visit www.allaboutcookies.org.

 _How will we use the information we collect?_

Art Review Ltd. uses your Personal Data to provide you with a customised Web experience and to provide services to you. Such services include sending you marketing messages if you have given us permission to do so, processing your answers to quizzes and other competitions, and sending electronic newsletters and promotional e-mails to you. We also use Personal Data for customer service messages, and to notify you about updates to our services and to respond to your requests.

We may create Anonymous Data records from Personal Data by excluding information (such as your name) that makes the data personally identifiable to you. We use this Anonymous Data to perform statistical analyses of users’ aggregate behaviour so that we may enhance the content of our services and improve site navigation. Art Review Ltd. reserves the right to use and disclose Anonymous Data to third parties at its discretion, in aggregate form.

If you elect to receive communications from us we may periodically send you free newsletters and e-mails that directly promote the use of our sites or the purchase of our products or services and may contain advertisements for third parties.

 _Do we share your Personal Data with other companies?_

Except as otherwise stated in this Privacy Policy and in our Privacy Notices where you give us your consent, we do not sell, trade, or rent the Personal Data collected from our services to third parties.

However, we will share your Personal Data with our third party suppliers who need to process your data in order to fulfil your request, such as to charge your credit card (if authorised by you), fill your order, and deliver electronic newsletters and promotional e-mails. These third parties are required under contract not to use your Personal Data other than to provide the services requested by Art Review Ltd. and to guarantee to our satisfaction that they have sufficient processes in place to ensure the security of your data whilst it is in their care.

You expressly consent to the sharing of your Personal Data with our contractors and third party service providers for the purpose of providing services to you.

If you send a testimonial or comment to us, we may post it on our site or use it in advertising materials. We will attribute your testimonial to you by posting your first and last initial or your first name and last initial next to your testimonial on our site or advertising materials, if provided.

Regardless of any choices you make regarding your Personal Data Art Review Ltd. may disclose Personal Data if it believes in good faith that such disclosure is necessary to (a) comply with relevant laws or to respond to subpoenas or warrants served on us; or (b) protect or defend the rights or property of ArtReview Ltd. or users of our services.

If another company acquires our company or our assets, that company will possess the Personal Data collected by it and us and will assume the rights and obligations regarding your Personal Data as described in this Privacy Policy and the terms under which you submitted your data.

If you provide Art Review Ltd. with your contact details and agree to receive promotional messages, we may share your details with our affiliates or third-party businesses that offer goods or services that we believe may be of interest to our customers. Many customers appreciate the offerings they receive from such third parties; however, we allow you to opt out at any time of having your Personal Data shared with affiliated or unaffiliated third parties for the purpose of sending you relevant information.

 _Changing your mind about marketing messages and keeping your details up-to-date_

We offer you choices regarding the collection, use, and sharing of your Personal Data. When you register on one of our sites or respond to one of our communications or offers, we will ask you if you want to receive future communications from us. You may indicate consent to receipt of these communications by entering your personal details and choosing what information you would like to receive, or by not ticking the opt-out box provided. Under the EU General Data Protection Regulation you also have the right to revoke or amend any consent you have provided allowing us to store and use your personal data. Should you decide to stop receiving further communications from us, you will have the opportunity to opt-out by following the unsubscribe instructions provided in the email you receive or, on some of our sites, by going to “Edit Your Profile”, or “My Account” after you have logged in.

Despite your indicated communication preferences, we may send you notice of any updates to our Terms of Use or Privacy Policy. If you are contacting us by email, or by post please be sure to include your full name and address in order in your opt-out request in order to allow us to process your request for any changes to your preferences. Note that we may retain changed or deleted information in our archives, but we will not keep it longer than is necessary.

 _Where is your information processed and how do we keep your Personal Data secure?_

Your Personal Data may be processed both in and outside of your own country. When you submit your details and in whichever country you are situated you agree to the data being transferred to the UK and processed under the terms of the UK Data Protection Act 1998 and the Privacy and Electronic Communications (EC Directive) Regulations 2003 which stem from European Directives 95/46/EC and 2002/58/EC respectively. If you are not in agreement please do not give us your personal details.

Art Review Ltd. is committed to protecting the security of your Personal Data. We use a variety of industry-standard security technologies and procedures to help protect your Personal Data from unauthorised access, use, or disclosure.

On our sites, when collecting your credit card information for online purchases, Art Review Ltd. enables the use of Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology and industry-standard secured-server transactions that encrypt your Personal Data. To verify that you have a secure server connection, look for the locked padlock symbol at the bottom of your browser window or the HTTPS-prefix in the URL.

Art Review Ltd. has implemented other industry-standard electronic means of protecting your Personal Data. We store Personal Data behind a firewall, a barrier designed to prevent outsiders from accessing our servers. We may also require you to enter a password to access or update your account information. In addition, Art Review Ltd. protects your Personal Data from unauthorised physical access by storing your Personal Data in a controlled facility.

Except as provided elsewhere in this Privacy Policy, Art Review Ltd. limits access to Personal Data in electronic databases to those persons (including employees and contractors) in ArtReview Ltd.’s organisation who have a business need for such access and those persons are under contract to keep your data secure.

Even though Art Review Ltd. has taken significant steps to ensure that your Personal Data is not intercepted, accessed, used, or disclosed by unauthorised persons, you should know that Art Review Ltd. cannot eliminate security risks associated with Personal Data.

 _Access to your Personal Data_

The EU General Data Protection Regulation gives you the right to access information held about you. You may ask us to make any necessary changes to ensure that it is accurate and kept up to date. You may also ask for erasure or blocking of data that have been processed unlawfully, to object to the processing of your personal data, or if you have any questions about our Privacy Policy. If you wish to see the information we hold about you, please contact us in writing, by email or by telephone:

The Data Protection Compliance Officer

Art Review Ltd.

1 Honduras Street,

London, EC1Y 0TH, United Kingdom

E-mail: privacy@artreview.com

Telephone: +44 20 7490 8138

We will respond to your request for access to personal data within one month of the day on which it was made. These changes will be effective immediately for new users of our services.

Please note that at all times you are responsible for updating your Personal Data to provide us with your most current e-mail and postal address. In the event that the last e-mail or postal address that you have provided us is not valid, or for any reason is not capable of delivering to you the notice described above, our despatch of the e-mail or letter containing such notice will nonetheless constitute effective notice of the changes described in the notice. In any event, changes to this Privacy Policy may affect our use of Personal Data that you provided us prior to our notification to you of the changes. If you do not wish to permit changes in our use of your Personal Data, you must notify us prior to the effective date of the changes that you wish to deactivate your account with us.

This Privacy Policy was last revised in May 2018

Reference C1
